[{"answer": " We missed the deadline", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I don't think so", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Did you send in all of the deposit checks", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " What do you mean, you think so", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What do you mean, you think so", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The wedding cake check", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hotel for my parents, the tent, the band, the Judge..", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " You forgot the tent", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I think so", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I didn't mean to my friend. I'm sorry", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm not playing around. I forgot", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He is", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He's my friend. He's not a moron", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He's a great chef", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You expect more what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm not going to marry you with the smell of prostitutes on my body", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You will not be common!!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " We're leaving from my house in three hours. If you want to come, get your numbers in order by then", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " No first of all. I'm not in a game mood", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm not. What's the problem", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What kind of seats can we have", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So what do we do", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Go down where", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You go down there", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Go down to the seat place and straighten this out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend brought up divorce statistics", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "The hell you didn't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The hell I did", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "The hell I did", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What is wrong with you people? I'm a helper here", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That's the whole point. They rarely work out. But on occasion they do. And when they do, they do big", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That's sweet", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well you should", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Just a bit of organizing", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah. Nesting", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "False", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Not true", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "If I'm the king of that place, I say to myself, King, I say to myself, King... Take a good look around. What do I see", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Then what do they have", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "that place doesn't have a King", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "They have a president. A Benjamin Yahoo something", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "The Israelis can protect themselves. They got the that place thing happening. that place's for real, man. They scalp babies", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What? What's your point", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "The bucks gonna stop right here.  If my son doesn't know the six that place states, if he has trouble with geography, I won't stick it in his face. I'll help the little guy. I'll put him in the car and take him out there. I'll take him to that place for a big Lobster dinner, go skiing in that place, hot dogs at Yankee Stadium... I won't stare him down", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I won't do it", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Don't ever stare him down", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Don't eyeball your kids", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " What are you talking about", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Just wait a second. Wait one second. Okay. What are you doing", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Why?  Why? She's dead. Why are you calling an ambulance", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "You're a lying deviant. What did you do?", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Why was the floor wet", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "The floor was wet. She slipped", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I don't know why the floor was wet", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Stop it! Listen to me. Let's just take a second here and take hold of the situation, OK? Let's just review our options here", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Call the police. Okay, that's one option", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Call the police. Okay, that's one option", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Yes sir, there sure is an option here. There are always options", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Nobody knows she's here. I called her personally. Nobody knows", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Nobody knows", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "that place. Devil's Playground. The Black Bitch. All day every day.  Where's my friend", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "She's still working", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "We've already done this", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Don't point at me", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I have plenty of friends", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "I have plenty of friends", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "The hell I don't", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " What about the chairs", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": " What okay", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Are you guys gonna fill this place with kids? You sure got room for them", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Take your time. I wish I had", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Who? What are you talking about", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": " Nobody's smoking anybody out", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "my friend! Calm down", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "It has worked", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": " You will not screw this up", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Don't you fucking threaten me", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Don't you fucking threaten me", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "You go home", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "We heard there was some arguing going on. Some loud talk", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "What were you talking about", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "He is not cracking up", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "What did you ask me", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "What is the question you asked me", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Yes, you did. Now that is the question! That is exactly the question we should be asking ourselves. You tell me my friend. What have we done", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "I don't understand where this personal attack is coming from..", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Nothing happened in that place", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Take care of business", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "And what does that mean?  Are you insane?!  You think I would hurt my friend?! She's the mother of those kids! What is wrong with you", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "A move", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "my friend and my friend were not terribly prudent in terms of providing for the possibility of the unforeseen", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "I'm talking about Life insurance. I'm talking about money", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "Get away from me", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "I don't want your help", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": " my friend we've got to cancel, we have to put it off", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "Do you love me", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "My God. You've got to call the police, tell them it was an accident. Where is she", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "You left a dead prostitute out in the desert? Alone", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": " I'm talking about some bad, bad, very bad things. Bad things! Those are bad fucking things", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "Fine? Fine what", "qsentId": 104}, {"answer": "So what do we do", "docId": "Very-Bad-Things.txt", "asentId": 107, "question": "Move the bodies", "qsentId": 106}]